

# Abiodun Segun

Front End Developer

#### **INFO**

#### **Address**

17 Ajibade oke, Ajao estate Lagos.

#### **Phone**

0810-997-0175

#### **Email**

abiodun\_segun10@yahoo.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/segun-abiodun-3987381b7/



github.com/realshegz-github

#### LANGUAGES

English & Yoruba

#### **SKILLS**

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Trello, React, Chakra UI, Git, GitHub

Good communication skill, Solution oriented, Teamwork and collaboration, Technical Report Writing

#### **PROFILE**

Innovative Front End Developer with 2 years experience building and maintaining websites and web applications using web technologies such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript plus modern libraries and frameworks.

I have good interpersonal skills, am an excellent team worker and am keen and very willing to learn and develop new skills.

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

## Front End Developer, Phasecurve Technology

June 2022 - present

**Phasecurve Technology** is a Nigerian company focused on developing software to solve real business problems

#### Responsibilities:

- · Developing and redesigning web pages of the company's websites
- Creating new functionality and features on project using react.js and json-server
- Performing bug fixes and code reviews
- · Collaborating with designers to ensure design was efficient and technically sound
- · Working with client to develop technical solutions for business cases
- · Agile/Scrum Methodology

### Front End Developer (Intern), identity Pass Identity Pass

March 2022 - May 2022

**Identity Pass** is an IT service for compliance and security infrastructure for Africa **Responsibilities**:

- Learning and working with new development tool (GraphQI)
- Frequent design meetings and collaborating on projects.
- · Fixing code issues or bugs that arise
- · Agile/SCRUM Methodology.

#### Software Developer fellow, The Bulb Africa

May 2021 - December 2021

**The Bulb** is a tech talent incubator and a platform that addresses the shortage of African tech talents.

#### Responsibilities:

- · Writing and maintaining code, learning codebase and improving my coding skills.
- Frequent design meetings and collaborating on projects.
- Analyze the structure and design of web pages.
- Assembled web pages with basic components using react.
- Track project using GitHub

#### **EDUCATION**

National Open University of Nigeria, Victoria Island, Lagos

2020

Degree: B.sc Entrepreneurship and Business Management

Igbobi College Yaba, Lagos

2012

Certificate: WASSCE

Linsy Nursery & primary School, Igbo Efon Lekki, Lagos

2005

Certificate: First School Leaving Certificate

#### **REFERENCES**

- Engr Abiodun Olufemi Director of Bogus Worldlink Ventures 08053563731
- Mr Ayobami Joseph Director of Bamyx Technology 08165983685